http://kidsflysafe.com/privacy-policy/

Kids Fly Safe
CARES Airplane Safety Harness for Children. The only easy, FAA-approved way for small children to fly safe.
Sign Up for Product Updates
Email:
Privacy Policy
Privacy
KidsFlySafe.com is sensitive to the private nature of information you provide to us over the Internet. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your personal information while at the same time giving you the opportunity to obtain interesting and useful information, products and services.
Personal information may include your name, phone number, address and e-mail address along with other information by which you can be personally identified.
We also collect usage information from you when you visit us. Web Site usage information is not identifiable information. It describes how our Web Site is used and navigated, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page and the length of their stay. Web Site usage information also includes the domain names of browsers that visit our Web Site, time of day the Web Site was visited and other non-personally identifiable information.
Please contact us by e-mail at info@kidsflysafe.com if you have any further questions about our privacy policy.
Security
At KidsFlySafe.com, we believe that all Internet transactions should be convenient, reliable and secure. When you use our secure checkout you can be assured that all of your personal information remains secure. Your personal information, including your credit card number is passed to us via a secure channel called a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). This high-grade encryption ensures that no one can intercept your credit card information while it is in transit from your computer to the secure web server.
Please click here to contact us if you have any further questions about our privacy policy or to stop receiving future emails, phone calls, or other direct communications from Kids Fly Safe.
What is CARES?
Find a Store:
© 2005-2012 Kids Fly Safe. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
